All right, guys. I just got my hair
colored and blow blown blown out and
blown whatever. A blowout. I got a
blowout. We switched to a all natural
like hair dye cuz I don't know if I said
that on the on here, but I developed
hair dye allergy. Something about the
black hair dye makes my scalp burn,
which is extremely unfortunate because
my hair is black and I have lots of
grays. So I either accept the grace,
accept defeat and turn into a silver fox
at my age or I remain a baddie with
black hair but extremely sensitive
scalp. Like right now it burns. It
doesn't burn. It's just like kind of
itchy a little bit in certain areas but
whatever. I'll just have to put on the
medicine when I get home. Anyways, Ariel
is 7 minutes away. So I'm waiting for
him in my car. I'm wearing this really
cute um crochet top.
It's from Reformation.
This girl Courtney Grow who I follow,
I love her. She's like a fashion
fashion um she's like a fashion vlogger
blogger. She's one of those that
everything she posts is cute and I
follow her for a while and she had a
collab with Reformation. So, I bought a
few of their stuff and I It's my first
time wearing this stuff and I really
like it. It's super comfortable, super
airy. Sexy. It's like opened here.
I love it. So, anyways, waiting for
Ariel. We're going to go to Palama Wool.
Yeah, Palama Wool opened a store on
Melrose. One of the guys that works the
store, he texted me saying, "Come by for
some gifting."
And I said, "Yes." So, of course, I
might do dinner tonight with Ariel and
Kylie.
this barbecue spot that we love. And
yeah, those are kind of the updates.
Yeah, those are the updates.
Ariel makes the best coffee and he
brought me one from his house.
Hopefully, it's not too watered down,
but he makes like banana cream
coffee. It's like so good. He just moved
really close to my house, so we're like
neighbors.
So, he's coming here, too. My god, the
Chanel show. Look at Mona.
Oh my god. So chic.
But it's like I just wish I was tall
because if I put this on, it just would
never look like that.
It wouldn't. I would look like a
chaparita.
She's everything. I love her. Okay,
hopefully Ariel is here soon.
Hey babes.
Okay.
>> No. No. Where did you park? Like in the
street.
>> Adidas. Oh my god. We should go into the
Adidas store.
>> Oh my god. We should send Kylie a
picture.
>> Yeah. But yeah, we're here. I'm here.
I'm 1 minute away from the cherry store.
Is that Is it far from there?
>> Cherry? No, I don't think so. But I sent
you the address.
>> Okay.
>> 8410.
[screaming]
[laughter]
>> Why is that always our little screen?
>> I don't know.
>> I love it.
>> I see.
He got the straw.
[music]
Why not?
But anyways,
I told them that you were making me this
coffee, bro. There was valet right
there.
>> Okay. Yeah, there's valet here, too.
Okay, let's try it.
>> And aren't we going to go to Maria Tage?
Cheers. So then I can pick up my car and
then drive you to yours.
>> M
>> I have to pay though. That's the only
thing. [\h__\h] We're always like a minute
late.
>> Anyways, we're here. We're going to park
and we're going to walk and we're going
to shop around.
>> You ain't going to say mommy. [laughter]
>> This one.
>> This is spot.
>> Oh, this car. Oh, I think this car was
going to get it.
>> Oh,
>> yeah. This car. Sorry. Sorry. We're
going to get out. We're going to get out
and see.
>> Wait, go back out. Back out and then go
over here.
>> He wants to make sure he knows.
>> Hold on. I'm leaving.
>> Are you okay,
>> bro? Wait, Ariel, this car be Hold on.
Hold on. Hold on.
>> Hold on. Stupid.
>> And then this car wants the car. Carter.
Ariel. This car behind you also wants
it.
>> Like, are we okay,
stupid?
>> And now this car got it. I I'm like I
don't even care. Like hello. Are you
going to crash my car?
>> Hi vlog. I know. I've been MIA. It
honestly [music] took me It took me a
few minutes to try to find this camera.
It was in one of my purses. I have
Gabriette's
wedding this weekend. Tomorrow, tomorrow
is the actual wedding. Today is today's
the um welcome drinks that she's having
at Rainbow Room, which is like [music]
an iconic like bar.
So, I'm supposed to be ready in an hour.
So, let's start. I'm doing my own glam
classic. My eyebrows are so hairy, so I
just spent an hour trying to find
[music]
tweezers, but I always find them. I also
have about
20 dress options. [music] so indecisive.
But I'm going to try them for you.
Donnie is in New York, which is kind of
fun because that means I can like be
crazy and he's not going to be home
[music] waiting for me. I'm not going to
be embarrassed if I come home late cuz
he's in New York, so he's going to be
asleep. [music] I'm going to meet up
with five stars. We're going to George's
house. [music] He's from London, but
he's visiting for the wedding. We're
going to go to his house first. Have a
few pre-drinks. Mang, remind me
tomorrow. I might have you pick up a
dress to bring to me or put in an Uber
if it's [music] close to you. Okay. Oh
my god. Stick and she's like almost her
glam is she got her eyes done already. I
better step it up. [music] Christian
Dior
Dior Forever foundation.
I've been liking this for my [music]
makeup recently.
I love this guy [music] lip blush.
Oh my god, it looks so pale. Obsessed.
We blend.
I like the Maybelline [music] concealer.
Let's blow it a little bit.
I like that it's pink.
Oops.
My skin is a little dry because I'm kind
of peeling a little
I see dude.
Huda hot beauty. So, I'm going to do
I'm going to start [music] with like a
white a white base cream base.
Me talking to you [music] like I know
what I'm doing. I'm so funny. I lost my
t muscle. Next eyebrows. fill them in a
little
cuz my eyebrows are almost like gray
[music] looking instead of black.
Also, I look a little pale, but I like
that. Okay, [music] it's my vibe. All I
can think about all day long is food. My
food noise is growing.
Going to elongate my eyebrows [music] a
bit. They're longer. Okie dokie.
[clears throat] Done.
I'm going to do the eyebrow job and I'm
going to do this one cuz my other one
makes my eyebrows like white
[clears throat]
tint. Oh, you know what I have to do?
Maybelline [music]
peel.
I'm actually going to put this in my
whole lip instead of just the liner.
Wait. Yeah, [music] I'm just going to go
everywhere.
Boy, my lips have color all night long.
I've been really into the no mascara.
This is just like a keratene one that I
get after their lash lift to keep them
hydrated and stuff. Supposed to help
them grow. I don't know that. But
okay, now I need my I need my eyeliner.
This pencil is purple.
>> Icky, look.
>> Oh my god. [screaming]
>> So pretty, right?
>> It looks It's just the one that I found.
>> Yes. But please,
>> I'm so into it.
>> It looks It's perfect. The color's so
good.
>> Is it weird that it ends before it?
>> I don't think so.
>> Okay. Cuz really that is the whole way
there,
>> right? [clears throat]
>> Yeah.
>> It's cute.
>> I'm into it. I need to get the thing for
under it.
>> The the pad.
>> Yeah, cuz it's flipping it.
>> Oh, yeah. I have the thing. Oh, purple
eyes. Come through.
>> This what I wore to our Oh, no. I wore
>> No, you purple's cute.
>> Mm-m.
>> Mix them.
>> Okay.
>> Purple's going to bring out a little bit
of green in your eyes.
>> Oh, okay. Okay. I You're so right. I was
like, this look different.
>> Where are you going?
>> To Gabriette's um welcome dinner.
Welcome thing.
>> That's going to be so fun. Have the most
fun. Let me show you my outfit.
[clears throat]
>> Where are you going? [snorts]
>> So, this little vintage store near my
house. They have like I was going to
tell you about it. I think you would
find cute little knickknacks for your
house.
>> Let's go. Take me there.
>> I found something like that I think you
would like, but I'm going to buy it for
myself.
>> Oh, okay. [laughter]
Do you guys hear this? That's Ariel.
It's my vlog.
>> Oh, that's sex.
>> Sexy, right?
>> Have the best time and take all the
pictures. I don't know. What are you
going to do? Because it is a little
naked.
>> What?
>> Well, it's hot, [\h__\h] But Oh, wait.
Actually, now that I'm looking. Yeah, I
know it's hot. You need your nipples
out.
>> Yeah, I have.
>> But what are you But what are you going
to do about the one nipple?
I I kind of like my other nipple now.
>> Oh, okay. Amazing. But I don't mind that
it's always just a you thing. So,
>> yeah. No, I think like I do have another
like dress that looks It's the same
fabric as that one.
And I'm going to try to lay I'm going to
try to layer it.
>> Oh, to line it.
>> To line it. It's a little bit shorter.
So, I'm going to put it on top or at the
bottom and see if I can line it so it's
less see-through.
Uh-huh.
>> And take it from there, I guess.
>> Okay.
>> You would you would have my dream day
when I'm not available.
[clears throat]
>> I went yesterday, but they were like
almost at their closing hour, so I felt
like I rushed my experience.
>> Yeah. Is it a big place?
>> It looks like it's going to be small,
and then you get in there and it's a
maze.
>> Oh, [\h__\h] yeah. I love that.
>> Yeah, me too.
Um,
>> well, send me photos of what you find
and if you see any dining chairs that
you don't want for you and you want to
show me.
>> Yesterday when I looked it was it didn't
look like they had like
>> big big pieces like that, but I'll I'll
look.
>> Oh, okay. Well, just tell me what you
get. You know, I love this stuff. Gives
me life.
>> I I know. Also, you know, I woke up, you
know, I woke up ranked as a 10th rising
fashion and
fashion and arts on Substack.
>> What? Period, [\h__\h]
>> Period.
>> I told you I'm proud of you. Your things
are really good and you write so well.
A
>> Wait, Vic. This dress is everything. I
wish I was a girl.
>> It's a really good dress.
Yeah, that's hot.
>> Also, you want to see what I just
bought?
>> Yeah.
>> It's on an Uber package right now
>> from a Facebook marketplace.
I'm going to show it to you and you're
going to copy me. I know you.
>> Of course.
[laughter]
>> You're probably going to find one of the
[\h__\h] marketplace that you're going
to.
>> What is it though? Like a the credenza
that you were talking about?
>> No, it's like a vintage like cigarette
dispenser.
Oh, how cute. I don't smoke.
>> I know, but it's for your guest.
>> Then where do you put it on? Like on top
of a table?
>> Yeah. I [laughter] I probably put it
like like when I throw a party, I put it
outside in my huge like my huge that t
that table upstairs.
>> Yeah. Super cute. My friend Broen said
he loves your accent.
>> Oh, thank you.
Thank you so much.
Hey
Okay. Well, have fun. I'm going to
continue with my vlog.
>> Okay. I love you.
>> Love you. Have fun shopping.
>> Sorry about that. Intermission, but I
just feel like I'm so distracted and I
need to focus [music] because I have to
leave here soon. So, the fact that I
don't have my [music] my liner, it's
kind of upsetting
because you know why? cuz I don't know
if I also I don't know if I have like my
black
the liner that I love like my black
liner.
Oh,
classic brown. Let me try it. I want
[music] to add all the colors in here.
See, this might be better
cuz I want it to look like a [music]
smokey
like a smokey eye.
I'm really sad about my my blue pen
that's broken. And then you put it at
the top.
What don't I like about my makeup right
now? I'm going to [music] spray my
beauty blender. Looks a little dry up
here.
My face looks a little dry. Okay.
What's one thing I don't like about this
makeup?
I'm missing blush. I don't like My
eyebrows [music] I think are too dark.
My eyebrows are too dark.
It is
crunch [music] time. People keep calling
me and keep getting distracted. But I am
almost ready. Megan is almost here to
pick up the doggies.
That way they're not alone while I'm
partying it up.
Okay, I'm just going to change. I don't
know. I'm not feeling this makeup. It's
like, of course, [music] the one day I'm
supposed to feel cute, I don't feel
cute. Oh, I need blush. Blush, blush,
blush, blush, blush, blush. Oh, I have
this.
I should have done that before the
powder, but I think it'll be okay.
>> Hi, M. You look so cute.
How are you? Oh my god. Hey.
>> Say hey vlog.
>> Hi vlog.
>> Look at your big girl.
You look gorgeous.
>> Hey you do good. How are you? Look at
>> look how big it is.
>> So I bought this choker
that I love because it's like a cross.
It's kind of gothy and you know [music]
you know Gabby's like gothy dark and
sexy. So, I think this was perfect and
[music] I find it to be so the way it
just falls on the neck. It's gorgeous.
I'm unsure about
my makeup, but
confidence is [clears throat] beautiful.
So, I'm confident. I'm going to add a
little more bronzer.
Okay, we're going to I'm going to charge
my camera cuz it's dying. Okay, it was
like cocktail like black cocktail
like evening cocktail wear for tonight
and then tomorrow says black tie. No,
like formal black tie.
>> So hot. I can't wait.
>> Do what you want to do.
>> Is it better?
>> I think it's better.
>> Yeah.
Do we think that like because it's more
on the straighter side?
>> I did a little accident.
>> Oh, I thought that was me.
>> I'm not going to eat my meal plan
obviously, right? Like we'll see when we
get to George's. There's so much food
being made.
>> Yeah,
>> I'm like I'm hungry.
>> I'm just hungry, too.
>> Where's Dond by the way? I haven't seen
him.
>> New York.
>> He's from New York.
Yeah, right.
>> Okay.
>> Wait, what? What are you taking in your
purse?
>> I'm taking a powder
>> like a
>> powder puff. A black eyeliner.
>> Like a powder like this like like the
Kylie one.
>> Just the Charlotte Tilbury one.
>> Should I bring this one?
>> Yeah.
>> Yes.
>> Okay. Okay. Lip liner. I want to bring
Lumi.
So pretty.
>> Yeah.
>> And a eyeliner.
>> I'm about to leave. So this is my
outfit. It's like kind of sexy up here.
And I know how YouTube is, so I'm not
going to like get in trouble with
YouTube. Makeup. Cute. And the best
accessory
is this feather wax feathers like almost
like a scarf bow situation
like this.
And it goes like this.
>> Get it.
Okay. Got to go. Bye. Hi, I got to go.
Good morning. Last night was so fun. I
did drink classic and I posted about it
on my TikTok, but you guys, I suffer
from severe allergies. Do I look crazy
right now? Put a robe on. I suffer from
severe allergies. Like my doctor was
like, "Oh yeah, you have really, really
bad allergies." And last night, as soon
as I walked into this bar where the
welcome drinks were, my um my left ear
started buzzing almost like when you
have tin [music]
tinitus, tinitus, I don't know the name
tinus, whatever. Tinitus, what is
called?
And [music]
it kind of ruined the night for me a bit
for the first like 2 hours. It was super
uncomfortable. People were talking to me
and I was like, "Yeah, how are you?"
Like this. [music] Hopefully I didn't
look rude. I just was dying. Um, and
it's because I have severe allergies.
So, I did this nasal spray for sinus
allergy cold and I just like spray spray
spray. I just took a steam shower. It
was amazing. And now I'm taking some
suda
cuz
because [clears throat] if this happens
to me again tonight,
I will
actually like cry. It was horrible. I
wouldn't wish this on anybody. But
anyways, I'm about to get my hair done.
Today's wedding day, so prepare [music]
to cry. Julie, this girl Julie is coming
right now to do my to get a blowout cuz
my hair smelled like cigarettes.
And today is Hollywood Glamour, so I got
a new dress. Even though I had one, I
got a new one. Oh, so I'm texting Dio. I
send that with the [music] healed me.
Lol.
Sorry. I love you.
I miss you, Papa. [music] I'm so tired.
So tired. I mean, that shower felt
amazing, but I am exhausted. Purifying
mist.
I'm almost out. Anyway, maybe that's why
cuz [music] I spray a lot. And then I'm
going to do my serum and my moisturizer.
Pack it up. Oh, yeah. She should be here
soon. I leave in 2 hours cuz I'm going
[music] to Stasa's house to
take pics before.
I got a burnt I got a burn here. I'm
going to put some of this epicutis cuz
it's supposed to be super healing.
But you guys, as soon as I got burnt, I
put that cream from Paris, the biofang
bio something immediately cuz it was
starting to bubble and I [music] I
killed the bubble. It never bubbled,
which means if it doesn't bubble, I
think [music] it doesn't it doesn't
scar, right? I don't know. Ordering
Cerek Flown [music]
and earplugs in case I have to put an
ear plug. Oh, and I need deodorant.
Like a nice deodorant. What was I
saying? Deodorant. [music]
I need like a good deodorant that makes
me smell delicious all day long.
You want some volume today?
>> A [music] little, right?
>> Yeah, I think we
this damn dog. Get cozy, Cookie. And
don't help me.
Hey,
how cute is she?
>> They're so cute. Your dogs literally
make me want a little weird doll.
>> You're mean. They're very needy, but
like [music] I make them needy by being
like so
>> Yeah.
>> You know, it's my fault cuz you're just
the cutest thing in the world.
>> How's Whiskey now that she's a little
bigger?
>> I think it's good. They're [music] best
friends.
>> Oh,
>> they love each other.
Not by choice.
>> Not by choice.
>> Can I tell you what my grandma said
about our FaceTime?
>> Yeah.
>> My grandma texted me yesterday, like
probably 3 hours after we all facetimed
her to say hi, and said, "You'll never
know how much that phone call meant to
me." Dot dot dot heart.
I want to cry.
I want to cry. I want to cry reading it
right now.
>> Oh, that's so cute.
We're going to plan like a early dinner
cocktail wine with her this week.
>> She's just a girl.
>> Don't make me like
I can't.
>> I'm already going to cry. Wait, should I
put my Lumifi in now? Do you think it's
bad? I think it's been too I think it's
been I scratched my cornea like 2 days
ago, but I've been putting my drops in
and they say it only takes like 24 hours
for it to be fine and it's been 48. So,
I feel like it's fine. Also, like what
happens if I wake up with a red eye
tomorrow? Like,
>> exactly.
>> It's my hangover day anyways.
>> Yeah.
>> I wonder who's going to be there? Am I
going to find a husband?
>> I mean,
>> we're like too drunk, but like we get
too drunk to even like flirt. [laughter]
>> I just feel like I mean, I didn't see
anyone new yesterday.
>> Yeah.
I didn't see anyone like hot.
I know, but I think that was like more
family and like close friends.
>> Oh, hi beautiful blowout.
>> I'm so tired.
>> Huh?
>> Did you have coffee?
>> I had coffee. [music] I think
wave. No.
>> Like we should have you waves,
right? [music]
>> Yeah. Give a little glamour.
>> Yeah.
My face so tired.
I just came to believe I feel like this.
This part [music] right here. See? I
usually do
have the same thing.
>> Yeah. Maybe you need some sugar. Like do
you have a Coca-Cola
>> like that? I'll have one at yours. Yeah.
Yeah.
>> I was thinking like this. You know when
it goes like
>> the front like a [music] big
>> not huge but like like a slight width
instead of so many.
Does that make sense? I don't know. I
don't know what I want. What color
eyeliner? Should I just try to do blue
or purple?
Purple sky. Okay.
>> Right.
Try it. If I hate it, I could always
switch.
[laughter]
My camera died, but I'm almost ready.
Thank you.
>> I know I'm late.
>> I'm going to show you guys right now.
Okay, so this is a dress.
dress.
Wow.
Well, I only have this one,
but I don't know if it's too much with
the dress.
I think once this is done. Oh my god,
this is a little long.
Wait,
that was so close.
>> I just want to know if it's going to
like if they
I can't do it. Okay, guys. Well, I have
to go.
>> Okay.
I just don't know if I can close this. I
hope it's not broken.
I know.
No, I want to try to close the clip.
>> Okay.
>> Oh, see I did it. The clip.
I just want to make sure that
[laughter]
>> okay then I need perfume.
I just don't know if I like the [music]
necklace. I think maybe the necklace is
too much.
put my shoes on. Thank God for the shoes
that Sad got me for my birthday. This
ones,
they're amazing because
they make me so tall and they, by the
way, were so comfortable. Can't
complain.
I think this is too much.
[snorts]
All right.
[music]